Kishen Patel

GAME DESIGNER & DEVEOPER. WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

Address

401 Baxter Suites, Lyle Road,

Contact

patel.kishen28@gmail.com 0719173246



PERSONAL STATEMENT

I'm a 23 years old Game and Web Designer from Zimbabwe currently studying in Cape Town. I love everything that has to do with Web design & development, User Interface design, and I feel a true devotion for scripting.

I love working with people, specially if they have the same passion I have for what they do.

Why don't we work together? Go futher down to see why I am the man you need!



WORK EXPERIENCE

MARTIN EAGLES TEAM BUILDING: THE BIG DEAL

Game Designer, Web Designer & Developer, 2016 -now

I am currently working on a game for an international company using HTML5, CSS, NODE js and Javascript. I am the lead scripter on the project. This is a freelance project that I learnt so much from concerning javascript development and server management. The project team consisted of six members including me.

SELECT MUSIC: SIDEKICKS

Game Designer, Scripter, 2015-2016

This project was a mobile based game developed in the Unity Engine using Javascript and C# coding. I was the lead scripter on this project. The project team consisted of four members including me.



EDUCATION

FRIENDS OF DESIGN

Cape Town, South Africa, 2015-nov

FRIENDS OF DESIGN

Cape Town, South Africa, 2014-2015

Game Graphics & Multimedia Entertainmen

UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN

Cape Town, South Africa, 2012-2014

CBC HIGH SCHOOL

Bulwayo, Zimbabwe, 2006-2011



PERSONAL SKILLS

Social Commitment					0	0
Organization				0	0	0
Creativity				0	0	0
Communication					0	0
Teamwork						0



DESIGN SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop						0	0	0
Adobe Illustrator					0	0	0	0
Adobe InDesign			0	0	0	0	0	0
Adobe After Effects							0	0
Adobe Premier Pro						0	0	0
Blender	0	0				0	0	0



MARK UP & PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML				0	0	0
CSS				0	0	0
SCSS				0	0	0
JADE				0	0	0
PHP				0	0	0
PYTHON					0	0
JAVASCRIPT					0	0
JQUERY					0	0
C#					0	0
MYSQL			0	0	0	0



EDITORS & FRAMEWORKS

SUBLIME TEXT					0	0
ADOBE BRACKETS					0	0
NODE JS					0	0
BOOTSTRAP					0	0
WORDPRESS				0	0	0



HOBBIES AND ACTIVITIES



Reading



Footba



Gaming



Travelling



Hiking



Coding